<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Plugin Station</title>
        
        <item>
            <title>1.2.5</title>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:01:34 -0800</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>32</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.2.5</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <h3>v1.2.5 (01/06/26)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Make it possible to filter the plugin database by plugins that support macOS 26 (Tahoe). macOS Tahoe support information is gradually being added</li>
                    <li>Change the appearance of the buttons that appear at the top of the screen for creating/editing a plugin license key to be more consistent with other parts of the app</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where an error message about being unable to check for app updates may appear on startup</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where installed unrecognized plugins were showing erroneous out-of-date warnings in their details view</li>
                    <li>Fix a rare bug where the app may crash on startup</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.2.4 (12/21/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: The user can now view all of their installed manufacturers from the Installed Manufacturers tab in the left sidebar. After selecting a manufacturer from this tab, the user can much more easily contact their support, view which of their plugins are installed, uninstall all of their plugins, and more</li>
                    <li>A manufacturer's logo can now be clicked in various parts of the app, making it easier to access that manufacturer's information. It's now also possible to click the name of the manufacturer in the About section of a plugin's details screen</li>
                    <li>The Uninstall button in an installed plugin's details screen is now always a menu that unfolds to present uninstallation options much more clearly than before</li>
                    <li>It is now possible to uninstall all of the plugins by a given manufacturer via Storage Manager. Simply navigate to the Storage Usage by Manufacturer section and uses the ellipsis buttons on the right side of each row in the table</li>
                    <li>Improve the appearance and functionality of the search suggestion dropdown menu that appears underneath text fields where the user is searching for a manufacturer or plugin name. The user can now use the up arrow key, down arrow key, and return key on their keyboard to navigate through these dropdown menus</li>
                    <li>A symbol is now shown next to a selected plugin's supported macOS versions that indicates whether or not the user's current System Profile's macOS version supports the selected plugin</li>
                    <li>Improve the appearance of how the supported macOS versions look in the About section in a selected plugin's details screen. They now show as a range instead of showing each one individually</li>
                    <li>Visually separate the Uninstall button in a selected installed plugin's Options section</li>
                    <li>When exporting a CSV file for a user's installed plugins, the selected columns are now preserved and automatically selected/deselected every time the user exports a CSV file</li>
                    <li>Installed Formats are now sorted in alphabetical order in an exported installed plugins CSV file</li>
                    <li>The user can now expand and collapse out-of-date plugin manufacturers in the screen that appears when selecting an out-of-date plugins System Warning, making it much easier to navigate when you have a lot of plugins out of date</li>
                    <li>The app's splash screen now shows varying messages depending on what stage of startup the user is on</li>
                    <li>After uninstalling plugins via Storage Manager, the Storage Manager screen now refreshes instantly. Before, it was required that the user synced their installed plugin changes before the changes would be reflected in Storage Manager</li>
                    <li>Add a note to Storage Manager noting that Waves plugin formats cannot be uninstalled individually, so after uninstalling some formats it may appear that some files in those formats are still installed</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where hovering over the symbol next to an installed plugin's installed version would be difficult. There was only a very small part of the symbol you could hover over to present the intended message. The text that appears in these popovers was updated as well</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where macOS Tahoe was not showing as a supported macOS version for plugins that support macOS Tahoe</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where expanding a group of plugins in Uninstall Assistant would sometimes fail</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.2.3 (11/30/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: It is now possible to export a CSV file containing info about your installed plugins! You can either export all of your installed plugins, or you can export a subset of them by applying filters at the top of the Installed Plugins list. To access the window to export a CSV file, navigate to the Installed Plugins section in the left sidebar of the app. Above the list that appears, click the icon that looks like a square containing an upward-pointing arrow</li>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: It is now possible to use the Installed Plugins filters to hide or show only unrecognized installed plugins. To access these filters, navigate to the Installed Plugins section in the left sidebar of the app. Above the list that appears, click the icon next to the previously mentioned one</li>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: It is now possible to uninstall all plugin files of a specific plugin format via Storage Manager. Before, this was only possible in Plugin Station if you saw a System Warning telling you that you had an unnecessary plugin format installed. You can also open all of your VST, VST3, AU, or AAX plugin files in Finder via Storage Manager. To access these options, click any of the "..." buttons in the "Storage Usage by Plugin Format" section of Storage Manager</li>
                    <li>Many more UI elements now take advantage of Apple's new Liquid Glass design language. Only users running macOS Tahoe (26 and later) will see this change</li>
                    <li>Alter the messaging that appears when Plugin Station starts syncing installed plugin changes. This messaging makes it clearer what's happening during long periods of time where it may appear that the app is frozen, but it's actually not</li>
                    <li>When you reach the bottom of a fetched batch of plugins in the Browse Plugins and Installed Plugins lists, a spinner now appears to indicate that another batch of plugins is loading</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where it was possible to create or update an Activation Location with no name</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug in the Installed Plugins Filters window where the popup would appear too narrow on some OS versions, causing the "Clear" button to overlap with the title at the top of the popup</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where clearing installed plugin filters may cause the first batch of newly fetched plugins to load, but then get stuck loading the next batch</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug in the Browse Plugins and Installed Plugins lists where clicking the search field and then modifying filters would cause the loaded plugins to stay the same and not get filtered</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where plugin details screens were showing a blank value for the Supported macOS Versions field if a plugin was superseded or discontinued</li>
                    <li>Fix a rare bug where some users were experiencing a crash immediately after launching Plugin Station</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.2.2 (11/11/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Plugin Station Enterprise Subscription Plans are now available!</li>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Before, the highest number of System Profiles you could have on a single Plugin Station account was 3. Now, with Plugin Station Enterprise Subscription Plans, you can have as many as you need</li>
                        <li>To purchase or upgrade to a Plugin Station Enterprise Subscription Plan, please contact Support at support@julianmichaeltechnologies.com with information about your business (business name, how many computers you plan to use with Plugin Station, etc.) so that we can assist you</li>
                    </ul>
                    <li>Fix bug where deleting a System Profile was causing the user to get kicked back to onboarding, only for the app to freeze and require a restart</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where deleting a System Profile was not deleting that System Profile's ignored plugins</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where deleting a System Profile was not deleting its corresponding Activation Location if that Activation Location had no license keys activated to it</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug on macOS Ventura where the Settings window was not getting dismissed automatically after deleting the System Profile that was currently in use</li>
                    <li>Fix cosmetic issues that would appear in the Compare System Profiles tab if the user had more than 2 System Profiles</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.2.1 (11/09/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add more icons throughout the app for more consistency with macOS Tahoe's design</li>
                    <li>Add mention of License Key Manager to onboarding process</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where some users may see a 'Failed to fetch plugin by ID.' error message and/or a crash when scanning plugins or syncing new plugin changes</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the Total Storage Usage chart in Storage Manager would appear to have way too many tick marks along the X Axis for users with hard drives greater than 1 TB</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where using plugin browsing filters and plugin license key filters at the same time was causing issues</li>
                    <li>Fix wording in some Uninstall Assistant screens to make their purposes more clear</li>
                    <li>Fix bug in various Uninstall Assistant views where drop shadows were getting clipped off and not showing in their entirety</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where the Manufacturer Name text field would go off the top of the screen in the screens for plugin browsing and installed plugin filtering</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.2.0 (11/03/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: Plugin Station now features a tab in the left sidebar named License Key Manager, which allows the user to more easily manage the license keys for each of their plugins!</li>
                        <ul>
                            <li>License Key Manager encrypts each of your license keys using Apple's Keychain and syncs the encrypted license keys across your devices using iCloud. Your license keys never touch the Plugin Station servers</li>
                            <li>Upon launching Plugin Station 1.2.0 for the first time, an Activation Location will automatically be created that represents each of your System Profiles. In Settings > Activation Locations, you can create additional Activation Locations to represent various types of iLok Activation Locations (iLok Cloud, iLok2 dongles, etc.) to make it easier to keep track of where your License Keys are activated</li>
                            <li>If you delete an Activation Location while license keys are still activated to it, you will see a System Warning telling you that you have license keys activated to a deleted activation location</li>
                            <li>Updating a System Profile's nickname/notes will update the corresponding Activation Location's name/notes, and vice versa</li>
                        </ul>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: You can now add notes to each of your System Profiles! You will see a text field to add notes upon creating a System Profile. To add notes to an existing System Profile, navigate to Settings > System Profiles > ... > Edit</li>
                    <li>Some parts of Plugin Station now have animations to make screen transitions appear more fluid</li>
                    <li>Start caching the image that displays at the top of a plugin's details screen so that it appears more quickly on subsequent reloads</li>
                    <li>Most macOS Menu Bar options now show icons alongside their titles. Many menus throughout the app also have icons as well. This was done because many menu options now show icons as of macOS 26.0. These icons will not appear in macOS Ventura (13) through Sequoia (15)</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug in Storage Manager where clicking the "See All" button in the Largest Plugins section would cause the app to freeze and require a Force Quit</li>
                    <li>Fix a rare bug where it was possible for some users to see an erroneous "Unneeded Installed Plugin Format" System Warning under some conditions</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.1.4 (10/02/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Implement macOS 26 (Tahoe) Support</li>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Implement a new app icon that visually changes depending on how the user has set the appearance of their icons. For example, if the user sets their icons to appear in Dark mode, Plugin Station's icon will now have a black background with blue in the outlet holes. While icon appearance does not change between modes for users running macOS Ventura through Sequoia, these users will notice that the tag on the Plugin Station icon's plug now appears blue instead of red</li>
                            <li>Adopt the new Liquid Glass design language introduced by Apple. Users running macOS 26.0 and later will now see these new Liquid Glass design elements in Plugin Station</li>
                            <li>Make various, subtle changes so that some elements of the app are more readable and glanceable on macOS Tahoe</li>
                        </ul>
                    <li>Implement support for plugins manufacturered by Waves</li>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Plugin Station will now detect the .bundle Waves plugin files installed on the user's system in /Applications/Waves. Existing users with Waves plugins already installed should see the app sync these plugins with their account the first time they run Plugin Station 1.1.4</li>
                            <li>Plugin Station can perform the same operations with these plugins as it can with plugins from other manufacturers, the only exception being uninstalling individual plugin formats. It is not possible to, for example, uninstall only the VST3 file for a Waves plugin because Waves does not make their VST3, AU, and AAX plugin files visible for each individual plugin. Instead, they install .bundle files that contain each format, along with WaveShell files that interface with DAWs to load these .bundle files.</li>
                        </ul>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.1.3 (09/18/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the app was properly detecting installed plugin changes and notifying the user about them, but was not actually making the correct, corresponding change to the user's account for some plugins. If you were experiencing this issue, please check on the plugins in question after installing this update. If you still experience issues, perform an installed plugin rescan in Settings > Installed Software > Rescan Installed Plugins and you should not see this issue again. If you do, please contact support@julianmichaeltechnologies.com</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug in the out-of-date plugins system warning. Next to the manufacturer of each out-of-date plugin, the app displays a button indicating the best way to get the latest version of that manufacturer's plugins. In cases where there were multiple options for getting the latest version, the button was performing the right action, but it was not labeled properly. For example, in some cases it would tell the user to open an installation manager when it should've told the user to open the manufacturer's Downloads page</li>
                    <li>Add clearer messaging during app startup to explain to the user what's happening in the event of a slower-than-usual startup time</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.1.2 (09/14/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the app would sometimes tell the user that their plugins are out of sync, even though they aren't. This would usually be triggered by navigating through plugin folders in Finder without actually making any changes to any files</li>
                    <li>Fix searching so that it returns a max of 25 results instead of the default 10.</li>
                    <li>Fix bug in Storage Manager where "Total Hard Drive" had a chart color assigned to it even though that color would never actually appear in the chart since it was covered by all the other colors</li>
                    <li>Make it so that black and white cannot be chart colors in Storage Manager because, depending on the user's color scheme, they will not be visible</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug on macOS Ventura where searching for plugins will sometimes flicker the fetched plugins, and then show others as if no search occurred</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug on macOS Ventura where opening the Browse Plugins or Installed Plugins List will sometimes cause a loop where batches are repeatedly fetched back to back, as opposed to the intended behavior where more plugins only load if the user scrolls down</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug on macOS Ventura where many buttons were not sizing properly and were appearing vertically shorter than intended</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug on macOS Ventura where, after rescanning DAWs, the window that appears would truncate most of its content instead of showing the user the DAWs that were found</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.1.1 (09/10/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the icon was not appearing for the System Profiles tab in App Settings for macOS Ventura and Sonoma</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug in Uninstall Assistant on macOS Ventura where the uninstall window would reappear and become undismissable after uninstalling plugins</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the user would see an error message after launching the app if they did not have one of the default plugin folders on their system</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.1.0 (09/09/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: Plugin Station now features a tab in the left sidebar named Uninstall Assistant, which allows the user to uninstall many plugins at a time</li>
                    <li>The user is no longer required to open a Finder window to delete plugin files. Instead, Plugin Station handles plugin uninstallation automatically</li>
                    <li>The app now shows a message in the bottom left corner when installed plugins are altered, as opposed to instantly updating when a change is detected. The user has to click this message in order to sync the changes</li>
                    <li>The user is no longer prompted to use an installation manager for uninstalling if that installation manager is not capable of uninstalling plugins</li>
                    <li>Manufacturer logos are now cached so that when they appear shortly after having already appeared, they load instantly</li>
                    <li>Show the user which plugin's data is being updated while the app is updating detected plugin changes</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug on macOS Ventura where Filter and Sort Options popups repeatedly appear and dismiss after clicking the button to present them</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where uninstalling or installing many plugins at a time while the app is running was causing unexpected behavior</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.0.14 (08/15/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix bug where an Out-Of-Date Plugins System Warning would show plugin formats as being out of date even if they weren't, but another one was. For example, if a plugin's VST file was out of date it would show that, but it would also show the VST3, AU, and AAX files as being out of date, even if they weren't</li>
                    <li>Clicking an Out-Of-Date Plugin Notification will now open up that notification in the Notifications list within the app</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where an error message regarding an unexpectedly missing "Installed Manufacturer" would appear for some users after making changes to installed plugins during and not during app operation</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.0.13 (08/15/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix bug where some plugins were appearing multiple times in the installed plugins list</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where some DAWs were unexpectedly going undetected during DAW scanning. NOTE: If you were experiencing this issue, please rescan your DAWs via Settings > Installed Software > Rescan Installed DAWs so that Plugin Station can detect your previously unreecognized DAWs</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where DAW version numbers were not being formatted correctly</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.0.12 (08/14/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>NEW FEATURE: Due to popular demand, you can now "Ignore" plugins in System Warnings! Simply click the Ignore button next to a plugin in a System Warning to ignore it, or use the checkboxes to select and ignore multiple plugins at a time. NOTE: Only recognized plugins with known manufacturer information can be ignored, and ignoring a plugin will stop it from triggering any and all system warnings</li>
                    <li>Add a "Release Notes" button to the Plugin Station tab in the macOS Menu Bar. Click this button to open your browser and view a page where you can see the release notes for every version of Plugin Station</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>v1.0.11 (08/11/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where a "Trouble reaching the Branch servers, please try again shortly." error message was occasionally being shown to some users when clicking a plugin in the Browse Plugins list</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.10 (08/08/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>The user is now prompted to indicate how they heard about Plugin Station during onboarding</li>
                    <li>The user is now prompted to provide a cancellation reason when they are cancelling their subscription</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.9 (08/06/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where a superseded plugin system warning would show up for plugins that have the superseded and superseding plugin installed. No longer will a warning be shown for a superseded plugin if the latest plugin that supersedes it is installed</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the app does not properly handle plugins that have the same name as another plugin in the database. This is now handled properly both during plugin scanning, and when changes happen during and not during app operation</li>
                    <li>Fix 2 bugs in the screen that shows when plugin changes are made when the app is or is not running. The first was showing irrelevant installed version change data when a single format for a plugin was uninstalled/installed. The second was affecting what would happen if 2 plugins with the same name were changed at the same time. Only one of the 2 plugins was showing up, now both are</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.8 (08/03/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Implement CMD + ',' keyboard shortcut to open app preferences to follow standard macOS conventions. Also add a 'Preferences' button to the Plugin Station tab in the macOS menu bar for the same reason</li>
                    <li>Further improve stability when a plugin is uninstalled both when the app is and is not running</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.7 (08/01/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where uninstalling a plugin while the app is or is not running may cause a crash under some conditions</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the app was not properly handling when an email address with both uppercase and lowercase letters was entered during account creation</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.6 (07/29/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix bug where some users experience an infinite loading screen after making changes to installed plugins and reopening the app</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.5 (07/28/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Implement perpetual licenses. Perpetual licenses can now be purchased, upgraded, and used in Plugin Station</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where AAX plugins were not being scanned properly</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where the user was not being properly redirected into the app after purchasing a new subscription or switching subscription plans</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.4 (07/26/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix bug where user may be stuck at app startup if an error is thrown after detecting changes to installed plugins</li>
                    <li>Add verbiage to Installed Plugin rescan screen to make it clearer that the preparation for rescan may take a couple minutes</li>
                    <li>Fix bug where enabling the Manufacturer filter for plugins but not actually selecting a manufacturer would cause a "Failed to perform search, received unexpected response with code: 400. Please try again." error message.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.3 (07/22/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug causing some users to see a "Trouble reaching the Branch servers. Please try again shortly" error message when attempting to purchase a subscription.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.2 (07/21/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug causing some users to experience crashes during plugin scanning</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug causing some users to be unable to purchase a subscription during onboarding</li>
                    <li>Improve messaging after plugin scan to better explain that plugins are regularly added to the Plugin Station database in order from most frequently installed to least frequently installed, and that notification emails are sent out to all users whenever an update relevant to them occurs</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.1 (07/14/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix a bug where Plugin Station would occasionally crash on startup</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where a plugin's details screen was showing an incorrect value for whether or not that plugin is available as a perpetual license</li>
                    <li>Update third party SDKs to prevent future bugs</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v1.0.0 (07/06/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>The first ever public, non-beta version of Plugin Station</li>
                    <li>Fix a bug where plugin versions may unexpectedly appear to have a "." at the end under some circumstances</li>
                    <li>The app icon now shows a badge indicating the user's number of unread notifications, if they've provided permission to show the badge</li>
                    <li>Fix various bugs for admins</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v0.1.0-beta.2 (06/30/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fix bugs with installed DAW scanning and presentation. <strong>In order for these to changes to take effect, the user must rescan their installed DAWs in Settings &gt; Installed Software &gt; Rescan Installed DAWs</strong>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Fix a bug where, for users with certain installed DAWs, Plugin Station would indicate that other versions of those DAWs are installed, even though they aren't</li>
                            <li>Fix an issue in the Installed DAWs tab where users with many installed DAWs will not see all of there installed DAWs</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Users will now receive an email, a macOS system notification, and a notification in the Notifications tab of Plugin Station when new plugins that they have installed are added to the Plugin Station database. These notifications serve to inform the user that they can now perform more operations with these plugins, and they are sent in batches by the Plugin Station admin that's performing the plugin creation. Clicking one of these system notifications will open Plugin Station and take the user to a screen with more details about it.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>v0.1.0-beta.1 (06/15/25)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Thank you so much for being one of the first people to ever try Plugin Station, other than myself. After almost a year and a half of working on this app, it's surreal to finally get it out into the world. I'm so excited to hear your feedback. - Julian</li>
                </ul>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/julianworden/PluginStation/releases/download/public/Plugin.Station.1.2.4.dmg" length="29040538" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="jU1Cm4GAYVuFEx/102Bi9Kc75gFTJNZ3FUbM0fu/FYnAjZJNmFyBP75T+lVct9BcqZORY4UtDEnX53DiUb7BBQ=="/>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>0.1.0-beta.2</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 June 2025 04:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>2</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.1.0-beta.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:channel>beta</sparkle:channel>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Fix bugs with installed DAW scanning and presentation. <strong>In order for these changes to take effect, the user must rescan their installed DAWs in Settings &gt; Installed Software &gt; Rescan Installed DAWs</strong>
                        <ul>
                        <li>
                            Fix a bug where, for users with certain installed DAWs, Plugin Station would indicate that other versions of those DAWs are installed, even though they aren't
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Fix an issue in the Installed DAWs tab where users with many installed DAWs will not see all of their installed DAWs
                        </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Users will now receive an email, a macOS system notification, and a notification in the Notifications tab of Plugin Station when new plugins that they have installed are added to the Plugin Station database. These notifications serve to inform the user that they can now perform more operations with these plugins, and they are sent in batches by the Plugin Station admin that's performing the plugin creation. Clicking one of these system notifications will open Plugin Station and take the user to a screen with more details about it.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/julianworden/PluginStation/releases/download/beta/Plugin.Station.0.1.0-beta.2.dmg" length="21435244" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="oswulyceZppFYZwBNx7+2g0+HHzUgyvpTYS0FVGojOCCodFGefDzQFlhTk15av9siZJmBSTKfDadLx+8koUNAg=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
